Oh. Good morning, Daniel-san.
Morning.
Welcome to Miyagi family dojo. You like?
This is really something.
Who are all these guys?
[Mr. Miyagi] All of Miyagi ancestor.
And who's that?
Ah, that is Miyagi Shimpo Sensei.
First Miyagi bring karate to Okinawa.
Like all Miyagi,
Shimpo Sensei was fisherman.
Love fishing.
Love sake.
One day, strong wind,
strong sun, strong sake,
but no fish.
Shimpo Sensei fall asleep
off coast of Okinawa,
wake up off coast of China. [chuckles]
[Mr. Miyagi] The Han family took him in,
taught him art of kung fu.
When Sensei return to Okinawa,
Miyagi karate was born.
Two culture, two martial art.
Two branches, one tree.
A bond that kept Hans and Miyagis
connected still today.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
[in Mandarin] Master Han! Master Han!
The Doctor is coming.
Stall her. Go.
Get Li!
The Doctor! Li, the Doctor!
The Doctor!
Welcome to Han Academy.
Are you looking to learn Kung Fu?
Never too late to start
even for an old woman.
We start with jacket on - jacket off.
Take off jacket, put on jacket.
I know he told you to stall me.
I did nothing of the sort.
He did ask. Sorry.
Go!
Where is my son?
Tea?
[Dr. Fong] I'm not here for tea.
Where is Li?
Kung Fu is very empowering...
Uncle,
with all due respect.
I already lost one son to your "path."
I will not lose another.
I understand.
[Dr. Fong] I know what Li means to you...
but I will not have him put in harm's way.
[Mr. Han] We both agree.
If you could only see
how Kung Fu helps him -
Each time life knocked me down,
Kung Fu helped me find my way back
to the proper path.
This is for you.
What's this?
I got a new position -
- at a hospital in New York.
New York?
It's a chance to restart for both of us.
Why two hats?
So you can give one to Li...
...when he finds the courage
to come out from behind your screen.
[in English]
Xiao Li, I'll see you tonight at dinner.
[in Mandarin] Very smart.
Your mother.
[Li huffs]
W--
[pensive music playing]
Were you even going to ask me?
[in English] Oh, there you are.
I'm sorry.
Xiao Li, would you like to
move to New York?
No, Mom, our life's here.
And how long were you gonna keep this
a secret from me?
And which one of us is keeping secrets?
I was training. Not fighting.
You practice violence,
you get violence in return.
You of all people should know that.
Xiao Li, there will be so many
other things for you in New York.
Why are you speaking in English, Mom?
New city, new language.
And you can leave all this stuff here.
Hey! Can I have your gloves?
Whatever.
["Home" playing]
♪ Darling, won't you take me home? ♪
♪ Send me shivers somewhere I used to go ♪
♪ Wrap my name across your mouth ♪
♪ When I let my feelings down ♪
♪ Darling, won't you take me home? ♪
[horns honking]
♪ Yeah, won't you take me ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh-oh ♪
[bicycle bell rings]
♪ Tell me, does your mother know? ♪
♪ Like the back of my car on a sunny day ♪
♪ You're the song on the radio
I never play ♪
♪ You're the words in my soul
That I wanna say ♪
♪ That I wanna say ♪
♪ Won't you make me say? ♪
♪ Won't you take me home? ♪
♪ Send me shivers somewhere I used to go ♪
[song fades]
[sighs] The boxes arrived.
Oh. It's nice.
[sighs]
[Dr. Fong sighs]
Go check out your room.
[horns honking,
sirens blaring in distance]
- [Li] Hey, Mama.
- Hmm?
I'm gonna try to find
something for dinner, all right?
I think I saw a pizza place
around the corner.
- Well, don't go too far.
- Sure.
And be careful.
I'm always careful.
["Tick-Tick" playing]
♪ Never knew life would be a big dipper ♪
♪ Always gotta be a little bit slicker ♪
♪ Got room to improve with the groove
Gonna make the beat quicker ♪
♪ Tick-tick-ticker ♪
♪ Why have people gotta be meaner?
Make things cleaner ♪
♪ Work on demeanor
Reach for the sky, be a dreamer ♪
♪ Life'll be a little bit sweeter ♪
♪ When the day comes
When you finally meet her ♪
[entry bell rings]
Can I help you?
Uh, yeah.
Do you guys have, um,
like, a stuffed crust?
[scoffs, chuckles]
[chef] No, we don't have stuffed crust.
But you know what?
I think I can help you out.
You need to get back in your car,
drive through the Holland Tunnel
to Jersey,
go 20 miles in any direction,
find yourself a nice,
crappy little strip mall,
and I'm sure you can find a stuffed crust.
Are you guys done?
[chuckles]
Hi. I apologize on behalf of these morons.
Oh!
- One of whom is my dad.
- I'm a moron?
Um, we don't have stuffed crust.
We have plain, pepperoni,
sausage and peppers,
Grandma's, Sicilian, eggplant.
Uh. Yeah. Pepperoni. Let's do pepperoni.
Pepperoni it is. Anything else?
Toilet paper?
[diner laughing] What? Toilet paper.
Sorry.
Context: I just moved in down the street,
so I'm trying to pick up
some stuff for the apartment.
Is there a place nearby that's open?
Preferably one where I don't
have to drive an hour to Jersey,
'cause I just flew in 18 hours
from Beijing.
[chuckles]
Yeah, yeah.
There's a bodega around the corner.
- Uh...
- Convenience store.
We call them bodegas here.
Oh. Weird. Cool.
Thanks. I'll be right back.
Uh, can I get a name for the order?
Yeah. Li Fong.
Welcome to New York, Li Fong.
Thanks.
- [entry bell rings]
- What?
Since when did you get so charming?
Someone in this place needs to be.
[diner] Ouch.
Ah. School starts at 7:45 sharp.
You take the L train to--
To Union Square and then I transfer
to the Six to Canal. Yeah.
- And then you see Ms. Morgan.
- Ms. Morgan.
She's gonna give me the schedule.
I got it, Mom.
I think.
Um, how about you?
First day at the hospital. Ready?
I got it.
I think.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
["Please" playing]
♪ I seen a lot of keys in my life, uh ♪
♪ Got people wanna please in my life, uh ♪
♪ Got varying degrees in my life, uh ♪
♪ If only I could seize
All the right stuff ♪
♪ Get rid of the disease in my life, uh ♪
♪ Oh, the birds and bees in my life, uh ♪
♪ What's the forest from the trees
In my life, uh ♪
[Ms. Morgan]
Take a deep breath and look confident,
'cause you never get a second chance
at a first impression.
Your mom wants you
to take the college entrance exam,
so we have a lot of work to do.
- [bell ringing]
- You two have a hall pass for that?
♪ One step, one step ♪
♪ We gonna build it
To the two step, two step ♪
[Ms. Morgan sighs]
♪ Can we try
For the three step, three step? ♪
♪ Can we make it
To the four step, four step? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
- [indistinct chatter]
- [bell ringing]
♪ Please, please, please ♪
[Victory Pizza employee]
Yeah, yeah. Screw you, Tony.
You know I'm good for it.
It's called professional courtesy.
Oh. Shit.
Your boxes are cheaper than you are.
Here. Let me help you out with these.
Thank you. No, it's okay. I got it.
It's all right. Um...
I'm Li, remember?
From last night, your pizza place?
Yeah, right. Stuffed crust.
- Yeah, that's me. [chuckles]
- Mm-hmm.
Stuffed crust.
Hey, um, how come your English is so good?
Oh. Well, my mom did her residency
in Hong Kong,
so I went to an American school
while I was there.
Mmm.
What, and now you're slumming it
here with me?
Yeah. Yeah.
[laughing]
Okay. Um...
Well, thank you.
I think I got it from here.
That's all right. I'm not doing anything.
Are you sure?
I do have a couple more stops.
Yeah. Seriously, no problem.
Made that many new friends today, huh, Li?
- Yeah, well, you know, day's not over yet.
- [chuckles] Okay.
[clears throat] I, uh...
[Li] Wait, like, this is so heavy.
These tomatoes...
Yeah, dude, it's really nice
not having to carry it all by myself.
- Why are they so heavy?
- This is great for me.
Okay. We got aprons. We got sauce.
Now we just need to hit
kitchen supply, and then...
[grunting]
Crap.
You study karate or something?
Yeah, kung fu. I used to.
It's cool, but, um...
yeah, don't do any of that anymore.
[Victory Pizza employee]
Yeah, you're clearly over it.
Just don't train here, okay?
- Why not?
- 'Cause you can't.
Mia.
[ominous music plays]
Long time no see.
[sighs] Not long enough.
Tell your dad he owes me a call.
Tell him yourself, O'Shea.
I tried. Your old man don't listen.
Guess I'm a chip off the old block, then.
Gotta go.
Who's that guy?
He owns that gym.
My dad owes him some money. All right?
Just stay off this block
and you'll be fine, okay?
One more stop.
[grunting]
[O'Shea]
Looking good, Conor. Looking fast.
You know, I just saw your girl, Mia,
out there.
Looks like she's moving on
pretty fast, too.
[laughs]
What are you laughing at?
What? It was funny.
You're right.
I need to lighten up.
- [onlooker] Oh, shit.
- [sparring partner groaning]
- [Conor] You want some?
- ["This Is It" playing]
♪ Now we comin' for the jugular ♪
♪ Punchin' ya
Homeboy, we boxin' ya ♪
♪ This is it, it's a hit
And it sounds like blaaow ♪
♪ How y'all chumps like me now? ♪
[music fades]
600? [scoffs] For a replacement part?
1200 new.
Okay. Forget it. Just these.
[speaking Mandarin]
What are you doing?
She's gonna give it to you for 450.
- What? What happened to 600?
- Mm-hmm.
She didn't know that your boyfriend
was from Beijing.
[both laughing]
- Wow.
- Yeah.
Mm-kay. Look at you.
You're so proud of yourself, huh?
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
You think you're my boyfriend now 'cause
you got me 150 off a replacement blower?
Uh, no. No.
I'm way harder to get than that.
- [Mia] Oh, okay. Really?
- [chuckles] Uh-huh.
But I could teach you some Mandarin.
I'm serious. If you went in there
and you started speaking their language,
you would get so much respect.
They'd give you the local discount.
I am the local.
Not in their shop, you're not.
And in return?
I don't know. Um, you teach me New York.
- Teach you New York?
- Yeah.
- What?
- Yes.
Dude, what? Look around.
New York is completely unteachable.
[chuckles] Well, they say the same thing
about Mandarin, right?
[pensive music playing]
Okay. Fine.
I get off work early on Sunday.
I can show you a few spots around town.
- Okay.
- [speaks Mandarin]
- [repeats in broken Mandarin]
What? What does that mean?
It's a date!
[stammers] Uh, no. It's not a date.
It's an educational experience!
- [grunts]
- How was school?
Uh... [sighs]
It was good. Yeah.
You know, it's school. [chuckles]
You make any friends?
Um...
Yeah, I did. One, I think.
Good. What's his name?
Mia.
- Mia?
- Mm-hmm.
["Trust" playing]
You know how to ride a scooter, right?
- [yelps]
- [horn honks]
You've driven a scooter before, right?
Nah. First time.
[horn honking]
Look, there's Simu Liu.
[horn honks]
Twins.
[both laughing]
[horns honking]
- [Li] Whoa, whoa!
- [Mia] Hang on, Stuffed Crust.
[music slows, stops]
[engine rattles]
[Mia] Ugh, come on. Are you kidding me?
[Li] What's wrong?
[Mia] The engine's shot.
[Li] Okay. So, how do we get home?
[metal screeching]
[speaking Mandarin]
- No.
- [chuckles] No, no.
[both speaking Mandarin]
[Li] Yeah.
- Perfect.
- You're messing with me.
No. No. It's actually...
I'm shocked, actually. Yeah.
- Great.
- What?
- [Mia clears throat]
- Hey, beautiful.
Hi, Conor.
What a pleasant surprise.
What's this?
Engine died.
- Who's your friend?
- Hi. Li.
Conor, don't start.
Don't start what?
Where you from, Li?
[Mia sighs]
Beijing.
You know kung fu?
[Li] Uh...
Little.
Okay, Conor, you can keep walking now.
We're just trying to get home.
It's been a long day.
Oh, so you guys are a "we" now, huh?
See, I didn't even know we were done.
Here you are.
Okay, um, this has been really fun,
but we're going to go.
[tense music plays]
Move.
Why should I?
- [Mia sighs]
- 'Cause she asked you to.
Li...
[train wheels screeching]
No, you guys are right. My bad.
Come on, let's let the lady pass.
[subway announcer] ...doors, please.
Stand clear of the doors.
Next stop, 23rd Street.
- Heads up!
- [grunts]
[Mia] Li!
- Conor!
- [Conor's friend chuckles]
[passenger] Oh, God!
- [Conor] Later, Mia.
- [Conor's friend] Good one, bro.
Dude, I'm so sorry.
Conor's a psycho.
[sighs] He's kind of the low point
of my teenage rebellion.
In my defense, he wasn't such a dick
until he started training at that gym.
[sighs] You just...
You can't step to guys like him.
He practices karate, like, 24-7.
He wins the 5 Boroughs every year.
What's the 5 Boroughs?
It's this insane karate tournament
on the streets all around the city.
You get big prize money if you win.
But don't get any ideas, Mr. Kung Fu.
[Li chuckles]
My dad told me a thousand times
not to get involved with him.
So, why did you?
'Cause he told me not to.
[gentle music playing]
How's your eye? Can I see it?
Sure.
- [blows] Hmm.
- What?
- Hmm. Mm-mmm, mm-mmm.
- Is it really bad?
- No, it's-- It's, well...
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Oh! What happened to Stuffed Crust?
Can you help him?
[sighs]
This is definitely going to sting
for a couple of days.
Ooh, ooh. Don't move.
So, where'd you learn how to do makeup?
- My wife.
- She taught you?
[chuckles] No. No, for nights like this.
She didn't much like me fighting either.
Let me see.
Yeah, I think that'll work.
Okay, from now on...
keep your guard up. Hands like this.
Hmm. Sure.
Take a look.
Wow.
So... how long have you been fighting?
[Mia's dad] Too long.
- He was the best in the city once.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
Now I'm doing makeup on teenagers.
[sighs] Ice it before bed, and then
sleep with a tea bag on it tonight.
Green? Black?
Lipton.
[gasping]
What are you doing?
You come to America. No fighting.
It was a simple rule.
[sighs]
I didn't have a choice.
You always have a choice.
[pensive music playing]
Get dressed.
[grunts]
[upbeat music playing]
Um, who is this person?
Your tutor for the SATs.
Enjoy your day.
[chuckles]
What's so funny?
Your mom thinks you're going to
get into NYU with these calc skills.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't be laughing
if I were you.
Have you met my mom?
Did she do that to your eye?
[horns honking, sirens wailing]
[chuckles]
[trainer] All right, Li. Dragon Kick.
[in Mandarin] Oh my god!
See the run up is key.
But the balance and the jump,
that's what sells it.
Now you try.
[sighs]
[grunts]
I don't think I'm going to master
this one.
You will.
One day, when you need it.
[grunts, chuckles]
[grunting]
[pensive music playing]
[school bell rings]
[Conor] Yo, Beijing.
How's the eye?
Looks like it's healing up nice.
Hey, don't walk away from me.
[tense music playing]
You know the first rule of karate, right?
You always keep your guard up.
[students] Ooh! [gasping]
[Conor chuckles]
You really want to do this, Beijing?
I'll take it easy on you. No hands.
[both grunting]
- [Li groans]
- [students gasp]
[Conor laughing]
[student 1] That was crazy as hell!
- [student 2] Do not get up.
- [student 3] Stay down!
[trainer] The Dragon Kick.
[Li, trainer speaking Mandarin]
See the run up is key.
[trainer speaks Mandarin]
[grunting]
- [groans]
- [students] Ooh!
Oh, is that all you got, Beijing?
- [Ms. Morgan] That's enough!
- That's enough.
[students chattering]
Hey, you actually want to fight, Beijing?
Fight me in the 5 Boroughs
where no one can save your ass.
- Hey, get off me!
- Let's go.
[Ms. Morgan] Show's over, folks!
[students laughing, chattering]
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[siren wails in distance]
- Huh.
- [cat yowls]
[thug 1] What we got here?
[thug 2] Yo, kid, get on out of here.
Hey, fellas.
Why don't we let the kid go home?
And we can settle whatever it is
O'Shea sent you here to settle.
Yeah.
[ominous music plays]
Victor, look out!
["North American Scum" playing]
Victor!
I told you, kid.
[grunts]
[grunting]
- [grunts]
- [groans]
♪ We're not, no ♪
♪ We've been on planes and on trains... ♪
[gasping]
[song slows, stops]
[groaning, panting]
[song resumes]
[groans]
[all grunting, groaning]
♪ We are North American scum ♪
[screams]
♪ And all the kids ♪
♪ All the kids don't wanna make a scene ♪
[groans]
♪ So where's the love? Where's the love? ♪
♪ Where's the love? Where's the love? ♪
♪ Where's the love tonight? ♪
[grunts, groans]
[groans]
♪ Take me back to the States, man ♪
♪ North American ♪
[song stops]
[thug 1] Let's get out of here!
[thug 2] Let's go!
And you better pay up, Victor!
And I thought I was going to rescue you.
[groans]
[sighs]
Here, helps with the healing.
[slurps]
Mmm.
Whoa.
So, you want to tell me
what that was out there?
I used to train kung fu.
- Would you teach it?
- To who?
- Me.
- [chuckles]
I took a loan from the kind of people
you don't want to borrow money from.
Now the loan is due, I can't pay,
and that was them coming to collect.
They're not going to stop.
So, what are you going to do?
I used to be good.
- Best in the city at one point, Li.
- Wow.
So, what happened?
Mia happened. Best thing to ever happen.
But it did catch me by surprise, so...
Needed something steady.
Traded in the gloves for the apron,
and the rest is history.
Most people don't know the moment
their life changed forever.
I get to see mine every day.
[pensive music playing]
Look.
I know a guy.
Promotes fights around the city.
He's going to set me up with a prize fight
with a purse big enough
I can pay my debt, keep the shop,
maybe even have a little left over
to pay for college.
- Listen, Victor, I can't help--
- Li,
I ain't got a shot to win unless...
you teach me what you know.
The speed, the flexibility, how you move.
I can't.
Why not?
Because I made a promise
that I wouldn't fight anymore.
I'm just... trying very hard to keep it.
But you're not fighting. I am.
[chuckles] Right.
Look, um...
I also know the moment
that my life changed forever.
And I replay it over and over in my head.
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[dogs barking in distance]
Here. Let me help.
No, I got it.
- [scoffs] I got it, Mom.
- Mmm.
I don't understand
why I have to go to this thing.
Never went to a temple in China.
New city, new traditions.
Mmm.
[wistful music playing]
You look good.
Thanks.
[wistful music continues]
[sighs] I miss him.
[line ringing]
- [line clicks]
- [Mr. Han] Mmm?
Hey, Shifu. It's Li.
[in Mandarin] How are you, Li?
Are we loving New York yet?
More missing Beijing.
The school misses you too.
Wait a minute...
Say hi!
Xiao Li!
Shifu...
[Mr. Han] Ah.
I've made a new friend here
who asked me to teach him Kung Fu.
I see.
Do you think Kung Fu can help your friend?
I think so.
Anything that helps others
and benefits yourself is a good thing.
[in English] Sharing your knowledge
is a good thing.
Hey! What can I get ya?
You're old.
And you're slow.
And your footwork's sloppy.
- [sighs] Anything else?
- [Li] Yeah.
You take more punches than you throw,
which I feel like you think
that's a talent, but it's not.
So what are you doing here?
I can make you better.
When do we start?
All right. Let's just do
a three-minute round, yeah?
Full speed. Just try to hit me
however you think you can.
[chuckles]
Li, you're half my size.
I gotta see what you're like in the ring.
Oh, come on.
I'm not fighting a 150-pound kid.
Well, you're not.
I'm 125.
["As We Enter" playing]
[both grunting]
[clattering]
[Victor sighs]
There's no kicks in boxing.
Learn to duck.
[both grunting]
[clears throat]
[music ends]
Since when do we close at eight o'clock?
[Victor, Li panting]
[Li chuckles]
Have you lost your mind?
You're gonna fight again? Really?
And you're gonna train him?
- It was his idea.
- He saved my ass the other night.
Yeah, you told me. He's the Chinese
Peter Parker. I don't care.
He can show me what he knows.
Keep me light on my feet.
You haven't been light on your feet
since you were 19, Dad.
Which is exactly why I need him.
You know you're giving him
false hope, right?
Better than no hope.
- Are you sure about that?
- Honey, it's one fight. Maybe two.
- Uh-- [scoffs]
- I can do this, Mia.
Uh-- [scoffs]
Unbelievable.
He gets his ass kicked, that's on you.
You hear me?
Yes. Yeah.
I think the whole neighborhood heard you.
[Mia] Good.
Then we're all on the same page.
Now if you'll excuse me,
apparently, I have a pizza shop to run.
[footsteps receding]
That went well.
First rule of kung fu:
everything is kung fu.
["Roadgame" playing]
This shop is kung fu.
[grunting]
Boxing's kung fu.
[Victor grunting]
Give me your arm.
- [groans]
- Lower.
Wrong side. Around.
Punch. One, two, three, four.
Horse stance...
Oh! Ooh.
- ...teaches control over the mind...
- [grunts]
- ...so that you can overcome the pain.
- Mm-hmm.
You're gonna be making pizzas all day,
you gotta be training
while you're making those pizzas.
I make a hundred pies a day.
I know how to make pizza, Li.
Cool.
Show me.
Squat. Don't bend.
[straining] How long am I supposed
to stay like this?
I'm going to lunch. See you in an hour.
Okay.
[Li] You got long arms,
but when you're in close,
you're not gonna always
have room to swing it.
You're gonna have to learn to
deliver power without moving your body.
This is called the one-inch punch.
Try it.
Don't worry so much about power.
Just focus on snapping the wrist.
[music distorts, stops]
["Roadgame" resumes]
[Li] We're turning you from a stone
to a stream.
[Victor grunting]
[Li] You strike a stone,
eventually it breaks.
You strike water, it keeps moving.
Always flowing, always fluid.
Order up.
All right. I got a large plain pie.
[phone ringing, beeps]
Victory Pizza.
What can I get for you, boss?
What?
You sound more New York than I do.
[in Mandarin]
...but downtown price is lower.
Please?
[both chuckling]
Okay, okay... [in English] ...take it.
[in Mandarin] Thank you.
[Mia] Let's do something fun.
- Yeah!
- [both chuckle]
- What about Li?
- Li is, uh--
One more time.
[grunting]
[Mia] Time.
[Victor] What do you think?
You might actually survive a fight or two.
[sirens wailing, horns honking]
[dog barking in distance]
- ["Run It Up" playing]
- [grunting]
♪ We all big time
Face on my Rollie on big time ♪
[grunting]
♪ My flow's unshakable ♪
♪ Run it up, run it up, run it up ♪
♪ Run it up, run it up ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me ♪
Oh, sorry. [pants]
Sorry. Um...
["Run It Up" continues through headphones]
Didn't think anyone would be here.
I got a loan shark, a teenage daughter
and a fight in two days.
What's your excuse?
[pants] I couldn't sleep.
So you always beat the shit out
of yourself in the middle of the night?
[rain pattering]
You wanna talk about it?
There's a old Chinese tradition
when someone dies.
You're supposed to open
all the doors and windows
and literally sweep all the death
out of your house
so that everyone else can go on living.
[chuckles]
[sighs] If only it were that easy, right?
[mournful music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
My brother and I got attacked
about a year ago.
It was, um, after a big tournament
in Beijing.
My brother won,
but the guy he beat wanted revenge. So...
[attackers speaking Mandarin]
...he got a couple of guys,
and they cornered us.
[grunting]
We were outnumbered.
[attackers speaking Mandarin, grunting]
One of them pulled a knife.
[Bo] Xiao Li!
[gasps]
Bo was screaming for me to help him.
[screams]
I froze.
[breathes shakily, gasps]
[dramatic music playing]
[screams]
[attackers shouting]
Now I'm here, and he's not. So, yeah.
I let him down.
[speaking Mandarin]
[mournful music continues]
You're gonna have to
let yourself off the hook, Li.
You deal with it,
or it's gonna deal with you.
Yeah.
[in Mandarin] Free pizza, freshly made.
Thank you.
Is she making fun of me?
Is it-- Is it my cardigan?
No, Alan. I don't know enough Mandarin
to make fun of you.
- Oh.
- [Mia chuckles]
So, are you guys
going to San Gennaro later?
I don't think I can.
I actually have to study
for this test coming up.
I think my mom's on to me.
[sighs] Come on. Don't be lame.
Li, just come.
It's like a New York rite of passage.
[Alan] Yeah. Uh...
Oh. [gasps]
And you're crushing calculus, by the way.
See? You have to come.
We'll be there.
Okay, maybe.
Okay. Then maybe I will see you tonight.
Dude, you are so in.
Okay, we're just friends.
Also, am I really crushing calculus?
No. No, this is all wrong.
I was just trying to
make you look good. Yeah.
- [upbeat music playing]
- [festival goers laughing]
Ciao. Ciao, ciao.
[speaks Italian] Ciao. Did you decide how
you're gonna make your move tonight?
I'm not making a move, Alan.
No, no, no, no, no. Tonight is the night
to make a move, man.
It's got everything.
Music, romance, sausage, peppers.
[gasps] Cotton candy.
[chuckling] Oh.
[pensive music playing]
[Mia, Conor speaking indistinctly]
[Alan] You smell that, man?
[exhales deeply]
Love is in the air.
[muttering] What else? Let me have a bite.
- Okay, I will.
- [Conor] It looks good.
Who's that guy?
Told you we were just friends.
["HOOLIGANG" playing]
[ring announcer] The winner of the fight
at 1:22 of the second round.
[ring announcer]
Winner by TKO, Hoagie "Cheap Shot" Parker.
[promoter] All right, Lipani,
you're up next. Five minutes. Let's go.
Got the ice.
Do we need anything else?
Li?
Why are you ignoring me?
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I'm already really nervous
and stressed about tonight,
and your weirdness is not helping.
I'm working your dad's corner tonight,
not yours, so...
let's just focus on that, okay?
[scoffs] No. Not okay.
Li?
What's going on with you?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask Conor?
What is that supposed to mean?
You two seemed pretty close last night.
At San Gennaro.
Alan and I showed up for a bit.
[sighs]
That's what this is about.
Look, Li, it's complicated, but--
It's fine. I get it.
Actually, no, I don't get it.
Explain it to me.
He doesn't deserve you, Mia.
Not even a little bit.
You know how sometimes
you have those dumb mistakes
that you just keep making
over and over again?
And it's like you don't even really
want to keep making them, but...
you do because it's there
and it's easy and...
- Last night--
- Actually, I'm good. I don't want to--
Last night was not
one of those nights. Okay?
He wanted it to be,
but I told him that I'm done making
those same mistakes with him because...
because I met someone
that I want to make new mistakes with.
So...
is that what we're doing?
We're making mistakes?
Best way to learn.
Oh, my God! Really?
- [Mia] We were just...
- [Li] We were talking about strategies--
[groans] And on fight night.
I-- I don't want to hear it.
[sighs] You're just lucky I have
someone else to knock out tonight.
["Don't Sweat the Technique" playing]
[ring announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
live from Queens...
This your plan to pay me back?
Wouldn't bet against me, O'Shea.
I already have. My money's on him.
[ring announcer] In the blue corner,
we have former welterweight...
Dad, if you're having second thoughts,
we can still back out.
You don't have to go through with this.
I'm not having second thoughts, kiddo.
Then why are we standing here?
'Cause you're supposed to get the ropes.
Oh, right. Sorry.
[ring announcer] And in the red corner,
we have the challenger,
the pride of North Brooklyn,
former Golden Gloves champ...
Sorry.
- ...Victor Lipani!
- [crowd cheering]
All right.
[bell dings]
I want a clean fight.
No elbows, no low blows,
and if I tell you to break, you break.
Gloves.
Welcome back to boxing.
Remember. Flow. Don't anchor the hips.
Tonight you're water, not stone.
You look scared to death, kiddo.
I'm not scared. I'm fine.
This is how I always look.
I got this.
- [bell dings]
- Box!
[grunting, groaning]
- Yes, yes, yes!
- Go on, Victor! Keep moving!
[groans]
Whoo!
You got it, Dad! You got it!
[man in crowd] Knock his head off!
Stop playing with him!
- Keep going! Come on!
- Come on!
You got this, Victor!
Keep it loose. Keep the pressure on him.
Don't trade blows.
You're taking too many hits out there.
Slips that hook.
Watch that one, all right?
This guy doesn't stop swinging.
You're the better fighter in that ring.
You've got this.
Stay focused. Don't let him back you up.
Use the one-inch punch, Victor!
Yes!
Go.
Yes, yes! Come on!
Let's go!
- Yes!
- Let's go, Dad!
- [Li] Keep the footwork up.
- Low, Victor!
- [Ortiz's coach] Take him down!
[grunting, groaning]
- [whistles] Get over it!
- [Li] Stay in control.
[Mia] Come on!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Let's go!
Yes!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Illegal blow!
- Illegal! Ref, what the hell?
- Hey, that's elbows!
- He can't do that!
- Stop!
[referee] Gentlemen, break it up!
- [O'Shea] Yes! Break his face!
- He can't do that!
- Illegal blow!
- Knock him out!
[groans]
[bell dings]
[muffled] Dad!
- [snickering]
- Dad?
Somebody! I need help!
Dad!
- Li!
- [speaking Mandarin]
Do something! Li!
[paramedic] Let's get him inside
right now. Code blue. Code blue, everyone.
Out the way. Out the way.
[paramedics speaking Mandarin]
Li? Li, what are you doing? Come on.
Xiao Li!
[Mia] Li, we need you.
[Dr. Fong] How do you know this man?
I was training him to fight.
[sighs] Xiao Li.
I thought I was clear.
No fighting.
I have to try to keep your friend alive.
[sighs]
["I Walk This Earth
All By Myself" playing]
♪ I walk this earth all by myself ♪
♪ I'm doing drugs but they don't help ♪
♪ My voice is nothing
When I'm screaming out for help ♪
[phone buzzes]
♪ I stretch my hand
But my grip just gives out ♪
[grunts]
[no audible dialogue]
[song ends]
[wind whistling]
[door squeaking in distance]
Mom?
[intruder screams]
[both grunting]
[whimpering]
[screams]
- Shifu!
- Now you see me, huh?
- [door unlocking]
- [Mr. Han] Go!
- Hey, Mom.
- Hi!
Surprise.
So...
this is life in the big city, huh?
I love your new home. Very hip.
Why are you here?
I just feel like the right time to visit.
[sighs]
- [knock on door]
- [door opens]
[sighs]
You cannot control
when life knocks you down, Xiao Li.
But you can control when to get back up.
We'll go to see your friend tomorrow.
Tidy this room.
Good catch.
- Go.
- [sighs]
[Li] Hey.
[Mia scoffs, sighs]
Mia--
Oh, uh, Victor, this is Mr. Han.
Hey, the legendary Shifu.
Li's been singing your praises.
Victor, I'm so sorry about everything.
Kid, it's not your fault.
Yeah, but the shop.
That's not your responsibility.
And, who knows, maybe it's time for us
to move someplace warm.
You can't do that, Victor.
You'd be walking away
from everything that you've built.
It's not walking away.
It's moving on.
[chattering on PA]
Ah. Chinese saying:
"Friend's problem is my problem."
We will find a way to help.
What was that? How are we gonna help?
Tournament start in ten days.
You will fight.
I'm gonna what?
In two days, you find us a place to train.
And where are you going?
- I'm going to see my friend.
- [horn honking]
[driver] Hey! Where you walking?
Sorry.
Wait. You're gonna what?
["California Love" playing]
♪ California knows how to party ♪
[song continues on speakers]
Hello?
[song fades]
Hello, old friend.
It's been a long time.
[door opens]
[Daniel] Excuse me.
You, uh, knew Mr. Miyagi?
Last time we spoke,
he said if I ever needed his help,
I knew where to find him.
I'm so sorry to tell you this,
but Mr. Miyagi, he...
passed away years ago.
I know.
I did not come looking for Sensei Miyagi.
I don't understand.
I came looking for you.
[Daniel] Look at you two.
Wow.
We took this picture in 1985.
Right here in this house.
He spent the whole night
talking about you.
His best friend.
The boy who put purpose in his life.
[chuckles]
I appreciate you coming all this way,
Mr. Han, but I...
My life now, I can't just pack up
and head to New York.
I mean, there's plenty of good dojos.
Yes. But I don't want Li to learn karate.
[stammers]
I want Li to learn Miyagi karate.
Li means to me
what you meant to Sensei Miyagi.
[sighs] I'm sorry, Mr. Han.
I wish I could help you.
- [horn honking]
- You will.
- I can't.
- You can.
You're not listening to me.
I hear you clear and loud.
I-- I'm not coming to New York.
I see you in the Big Apple.
[Li] My uncle
entered me into the 5 Boroughs.
You're gonna fight the most dangerous
karate tournament in the entire city?
Don't try to talk me out of it.
No, dude, that's so awesome.
We're gonna destroy that guy.
Watch out, New York!
Li Fong's gonna kick your ass!
Okay. Shut up.
I don't even know karate yet.
I don't have a place to practice either.
Okay, well, we can figure this out. Um...
How do you feel about pigeons?
- These are homing pigeons.
- [pigeons cooing]
Some kids inherit trust funds
and Lamborghinis, but me?
I get this.
The world-famous Fetterman Gardens.
Welcome to your new gym.
Yes.
["Mystical Magical" playing]
[Mr. Han] Cock-a-doodle-do!
Morning. Wake up. Time to train.
[mumbles, groans]
When did you get back?
[Mr. Han] Huh.
It's no Han School of Kung Fu,
but this will do nicely.
[Li grunting]
Focus!
Get low.
Log. Helps you block.
[breathing heavily]
Even out. Focus.
- [Li grunting]
- Jacket on, jacket off. More fling...
- [grunts]
- ...less toss.
[grunting]
[groans] Where did you come up with this?
Ancient kung fu proverb.
- Make do with what you have.
- Okay.
[Dr. Fong] I know why you're here.
- I know you know.
- Then you know I don't approve.
I know.
- [grunts]
- [Mr. Han] Get up!
[groans]
[Mr. Han] Jacket on, jacket off.
[breathing heavily] My problem is
that I see Bo every time I fight.
You still need to focus.
[straining] I'm trying to focus!
Jacket on, jacket off will help that too.
[rock music playing]
Go.
So we're just supposed to let him fight?
It is not about fighting.
It is about not giving up.
Not just for Xiao Li.
For both of you.
[Mr. Han speaks indistinctly]
- Huh? Huh?
- Turn around. Focus.
[Li exhales]
One hot dog, please.
- One with the works.
- Oh. Thank you.
Hey, can I get one of those too?
Ketchup, relish.
- Thank you very much.
- [vendor] Here you go.
[Mr. Han] No. Hot dog is bad for you.
- Oh. No problem.
- Never mind.
[Mr. Han] Hurry up. More training.
[grunting]
[rock music playing]
[Mr. Han] Get low.
[grunts]
[grunting]
Okay, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Okay. I know, focus, focus.
[exclaims]
Oh.
That was too wide a stance.
Karate is more upright.
We step toward our opponent.
Sensei LaRusso.
Han Shifu.
[inspirational music playing]
What brings you to New York?
Don't do that. You knew I was coming.
Xiao Li, meet Sensei LaRusso.
It's an honor.
[Daniel] This is interesting.
You do realize it's impossible
for a student to master karate
in only one week, don't you?
You have not seen student in action yet.
[Mr. Han] Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Good, good, good, good, good.
A week might work.
Our traditions are rooted in history.
You have a very good foundation
of kung fu.
But to win the 5 Boroughs,
you're gonna need karate.
We're gonna keep the movements
simple to start, okay?
- Front block.
- [Mr. Han grunts]
- Then you go side kick.
- Side kick.
Nice. Front punch.
Front punch.
Good. Han Shifu?
- Yes?
- [Daniel] Attack on three.
- Me?
- [Daniel] Mm-hmm.
And one...
[Li exclaims]
[Daniel] I said simple.
- This is simple.
- [straining, grunts]
These are new techniques. Don't you think
you should take it easy on him?
The opponent will not take it easy on him.
Why should I?
He's okay.
[Daniel] You asked me to teach him karate.
- Okay, first learn stand, then learn fly.
- [groans] God.
There's two of 'em.
[grunting]
[fighter] Oh, my shoulder.
[O'Shea] Again.
I already got the point, Sensei.
We don't fight for points.
We fight to kill.
[tense music playing]
- Strike. Hi-yah!
- [grunts]
Breathe.
Replace.
Hey, Li!
So, this is what they mean
by city views. [sighs]
You want to talk about it?
We kinda got in, like, a fight,
and now she's not talking to me anymore.
In life...
[gentle music playing]
...you have only one question:
Is it worth fighting for?
She is.
Thank you for your patience.
Hi. You guys ready to order?
We got a pie for Broadway.
What, you want me to ride the bike?
Come on.
[bicycle bell dings]
Hello?
Did somebody order a pizza?
Hi. Yeah, it was... it was me.
Flute of bubbly for the lady.
- Mmm.
Pepsi. Pairs well with pepperoni. Yeah.
Give him a chance.
[sighs]
So, this is the new gym, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, this is, uh,
Fetterman Gardens,
- where karate legends are made.
- [both chuckle]
You know you don't have to do this, Li.
You don't have to fight.
Yes, I do.
No, not for my dad.
And not for me.
I know.
I'm doing this for me.
And plus, if I win, that'd be
pretty cool for everyone, right?
[both chuckle]
Give us all that fresh start.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Do I have you in my corner?
There's just, uh, one problem. I, um...
I think I'm falling in love with Alan.
[Alan singing "I Want it That Way"]
[sighs] Yeah. Yeah.
[Alan] ♪ The one... ♪
I knew this plan would backfire.
[both laughing]
[Alan] ♪ I never wanna hear you say ♪
♪ I want it that way ♪
[Alan humming]
♪ Tell me why ♪
[rock music playing]
- New York, are you ready?
- [cheering]
Welcome to the 5 Boroughs,
where the top brawlers
battle it out to see
who's the best of the best.
And whoever that man is gets 50 grand.
[hype man] Mmm. Matches
are to eight points or KO.
Body shots are one point.
Head shots are two.
- [referee] Fighters.
- You got this.
[announcer] And here we go.
For the first round of the 5 Boroughs,
Li Fong versus Buddha Stevens.
[referee] Bow to each other.
- [referee] Ready.
- [supporter] Get him, Buddha!
[exhales]
Hajime!
[grunting]
- We've got one to the midsection already.
- [referee] One point.
[announcer] That is one point.
Buddha Stevens.
Welcome to the 5 Boroughs.
[announcer] Let's see if Fong can recover.
[supporter] Keep going, man!
- [referee] Two!
- [announcer] What a head kick.
[crowd exclaims]
[referee] Knockout. Winner!
Happy to be here.
[hype man] Tough luck, Buddha!
Yama-zuki. Punching block. Stronger base.
Windmill block more dynamic.
[both grunting]
- Hey, everything is kung fu.
- Yeah, well... No...
What happened to "two branches, one tree"?
One branch stronger than the other.
[announcer] Round two. 5 Boroughs.
Li Fong versus Queens Tornado.
That's the Yama-zuki punch block.
[referee] Stop!
Winner!
- [Conor] Next.
- [hype man] Easy win for Conor Day.
[announcer] Weather update. Tornado down.
- Li Fong moving on.
- [referee] Winner!
- [Victor] That's new.
- Do you like it?
Yeah.
- Hey! There he is! [laughs]
- Who hired this guy?
Her fault.
What's all this?
Congratulations.
You made it on the wall of fame.
[both chuckling]
- [sighs]
- Anything else I should know?
[clicks tongue]
[techno music playing]
[announcer] This is a glorified
sparring session for Conor Day!
- [Conor exclaims]
- [opponent grunts]
[announcer] Wow.
Making short work of the Lion's Mane.
Winner!
[announcer] That's it.
Conor Day advances to the final.
Yeah! There we go.
- [exclaims]
- [grunting]
- [announcer] Windmill block by Li Fong.
- [exclaims]
- [announcer] Lights out, Barrett!
- Winner!
[announcer]
Li Fong is moving on to the finals.
[Conor] Yo, boys.
[Conor's friend] Hold up, kid.
[Mr. Han] Sensei! Look out!
[Daniel] Li! Watch out!
[Mr. Han] Li!
[Daniel] Mr. Han, watch out!
[Mr. Han] You want some?
Let's go.
[announcer] That's it. Li "Stuffed Crust"
Fong advances to the final,
where he'll match up with Conor Day
one week from today atop the roof
of a skyscraper in Midtown Manhattan.
It's a showdown in the sky
where one fighter will win $50,000.
So, uh, how's the tournament going?
Good. Just missing one thing.
[melancholy music playing]
Your uncle says this Conor kid
fights like a tiger.
[grunting]
I have plenty of experience
with opponents like that.
[grunting]
You know the best way to defeat a tiger?
Be a bigger tiger?
Set a trap.
[grunting]
[groans]
Use your opponent's aggression
against him.
No, no, no, no, no, no. Better like this.
Come.
Hold on, hold on!
- [Li groans]
- Better like this.
Maybe in kung fu. But in karate--
Ready?
[groans]
There was a weird noise in my hip.
[breathes heavily]
- Punch! Jacket off!
- No, no, no! Come on! [groans]
Ancient way.
Yeah, I'm just gonna stay here
for a second. It's kinda nice.
- But in the Valley...
- Just give me a second!
- Miyagi way.
- [Li] Ow.
I show you this.
No, no, no, guys.
In Brooklyn, this is considered assault.
[inspirational music playing]
[Daniel] He's a good student.
He's had a good teacher.
[Mr. Han]
Teacher only as good as his students.
Sensei Miyagi taught me that.
I miss him.
Every time I have the chance
to pass on a piece of his legacy,
it's never the wrong choice.
What do you call that?
Oh. Uh...
It's fēi lóng tuǐ. It's Dragon Kick.
It's my brother's move, actually.
You gonna use it?
I tried it once on Conor already.
He countered it just like that.
He saw it coming.
Knocked me down when I landed.
- That's perfect.
- What do you mean? It didn't work.
That's how we're trapping our tiger.
Han Shifu, I have an idea.
What idea?
What did you tell him? Huh?
Conor will be expecting the Dragon Kick,
so we'll use it as bait to lure him in.
You need to learn to drop low enough
to avoid Conor's kick,
leaving him vulnerable. Then you strike.
Right. It's the third move
for the Dragon Kick.
He won't see it coming.
This is our tiger trap.
Wait, so you want me to drop low
under that thing?
You're gonna kick through it.
- [Li] Kick through it.
- Yep.
It's kind of impossible.
Have at it.
Great. Now get under the kick.
- Ow!
- Ooh. Hey, you okay?
You gotta get lower.
Life knocks you down, get back up.
Yeah.
I discovered this going through
some of Mr. Miyagi's things.
I think it represents the history
between the two families.
See, two branches,
- one tree.
- One tree.
This is why I came to train you,
so you could carry these traditions
into the future
and remember what you're fighting for.
["First Blood" playing]
It's yours.
Thank you, Sensei.
[Li] Hi-yah!
- [beeps]
- [Daniel] Good. Here you go.
You gotta go faster. Drop lower.
[Mr. Han] Stop hitting your head.
Yeah.
How much longer is this gonna go on for?
[music slows down, distorts]
How is this helping?
It's strengthening your quads.
[Li groans]
♪ If you want my body
And you think I'm sexy ♪
♪ Come on, sugar, let me know ♪
♪ If you really need me ♪
- Whoo!
- Wait, easy, easy, easy.
- Whoo! Hold on tight.
- [Mr. Han] Easy, easy, easy.
Hey, hey. Slow down.
- Whoo!
- Hey, hey, hey!
["First Blood" playing]
♪ There's a thunder deep inside of you ♪
♪ It makes you think it's all a dream
It cannot be true ♪
♪ Wheelin' hell! ♪
♪ Just call me, I'm alone ♪
One more! One more!
Let's go.
It's time.
Show us the tiger trap.
Under the kick.
Sweep the leg. Whoo!
[announcer] Here we go,
the moment y'all been waiting for.
Sixty stories high in the Big Apple...
the greatest city in the world.
[knock on door]
- Xiao Li. I--
- Mom.
Look, I know what you're gonna say,
but I have to do this.
I know.
And you won't be doing it alone.
[sentimental music playing]
Bo would be so proud of you.
I am too.
Now go kick his ass.
[suspenseful music plays]
[crowd cheering]
Xiao Li, ready?
Almost.
One more thing.
Sensei.
Two branches.
One tree.
[upbeat music plays]
[crowd cheering]
- [cheering fades]
- [heartbeat thumping]
- [cheering resumes]
- [thumping fades]
[hype man on speakers]
By the way of Beijing, China,
fighting out of moneymaking Manhattan,
we got Li "Stuffed Crust" Fong!
Go get him, Shifu.
[hype man] Out of Demolition Dojo...
We are trapping a tiger tonight.
...the reigning, the defending
5 Boroughs champ,
Conor D-D-D-Day!
[announcer] Once again,
here are the rules.
Eight points or KO,
body shots are one point,
and head shots are two points.
And of course, if you get knocked out...
There's nowhere to go, Beijing.
I'm not going anywhere.
[referee] Fighters.
[crowd chattering]
[speaking Japanese]
[crowd] Ooh!
[referee speaking Japanese]
[O'Shea in English]
Demolition in the house!
- [speaking Japanese]
- [grunts]
[announcer in English] Side kick by Fong.
Slipped by Conor Day.
- [crowd gasps]
- [grunting]
[announcer] Spinning hook kick
to the face.
- Ooh! Day looks a lot faster in there.
- [Victor] Ooh!
Two points.
[panting]
[grunts]
[announcer] Li Fong, having
a really hard time finding Conor Day.
- [grunting]
- [crowd gasping]
[announcer] Side kick to the midsection.
- Conor Day, admiring his work.
- [referee] One point!
[announcer] Li Fong takes flight.
Conor Day grounds him
with a one-arm body slam.
[referee] You can't do that!
[announcer] Down goes Fong and the ref!
[grunting]
[crowd gasping]
[Mr. Han] Xiao Li, get up.
Get back in there.
[Daniel] Come on, Li.
- Fight back.
- [chuckles]
[announcer] This is turning out
to be a wipeout.
[gasping] Come on, Li.
- There you go.
- [speaking Mandarin]
[panting]
Stay balanced.
Stay focused.
[both grunting]
[announcer] Block by Fong.
Block by Fong. Block.
Block by Fong. And here comes Li Fong.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
[panting]
[groans]
- [announcer] Point, Fong!
- That's our move.
- [announcer] Classic one-inch punch!
- [referee] One point!
[announcer] Li Fong is
finally on the board.
Can you still fight? [groans]
[both grunting]
[announcer] Okay, Li Fong not afraid
to go toe-to-toe.
[referee] One point!
Nice!
[announcer] Ooh!
Reverse-roundhouse kick.
- I taught him that.
- No, I taught him that.
[referee] Two points!
[announcer] Two points
for the kick to the face. It's tied up.
[hype man] This is the fight now!
We got a fight on our hands!
[grunting]
[exhales]
[announcer] Ooh! Fong counters.
Point, Day.
Point, Fong! He has taken the lead.
Ooh! Point, Fong!
[grunts]
[groans]
- Ooh!
- [referee] Two points!
[hype man] That's a head shot.
That's a head shot for Conor Day.
That's two points!
- Hey. Stop. Stay there.
- [Daniel] Hey. No, hey. Hey.
No, no, no. It counts.
- One, two...
- Xiao Li!
...three...
- Get up, kid!
- ...four...
[gasping]
Come on, Li!
[referee] ...five...
Xiao Li! Get up.
[referee] ...six, seven, eight, nine...
- [Victor] Yes!
- [Alan] Yes!
Let's go, Li! Come on.
[grunts]
[Victor] Come on, Li! Kick his ass!
- Come on, Li!
- Let's go!
- You can do this!
[announcer] All tied up at seven.
Next point wins it.
[grunts]
[tense music plays]
- [O'Shea] Let's go, Conor!
- [exhales]
- [speaking Japanese]
- [grunts]
[shouts]
[crowd] Oh!
[cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
[announcer]
Point, Fong. That is it. Point, Fong.
It is all over.
8-7, Li Fong!
Your new 5 Borough Champion.
Whoa!
- [grunts]
- [crowd gasping]
- Xiao Li!
- [Conor panting]
- [grunts]
- [crowd gasps]
Li!
[panting]
[exhales]
- Winner!
- [crowd cheering]
["Someone to You" playing]
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Xiao Li!
You did it!
We did it.
Yes!
Li!
Hey, hey. Uh, my hand. My hand.
Okay, all right, all right.
That's enough of that.
- Whoa!
- [crowd cheering]
[crowd chanting]
Stuffed Crust! Stuffed Crust!
[song ends]
["Episode" playing]
Thanks for waiting, everybody.
- We got two Sicilians and a stuffed crust.
- I got it.
Finally came around
on the stuffed crust, huh?
Limited-time offer.
I mean, you saved the shop.
It's the least I could do.
[both chuckling]
- Oh. Looks good.
- [Mr. Han] Mmm.
We're gonna miss you around here, Shifu.
- Wrong hand.
- Ugh.
Come visit Beijing.
We open third location.
You got the money, I got the time.
[grunts] Oh! Oh-oh-oh-oh.
Oh! [mumbles]
- [chuckles]
- We got a delivery for you, boss.
This delivery is going where?
["California Love" playing]
[knock on door]
- Yeah?
- Uh, pizza for a Daniel LaRusso.
I didn't order a pizza.
[sighs] "Thank you, Sensei."
[sighs]
"If you ever need my help,
you know where to find me."
"By the way, you owe $1100 plus tip."
[scoffs] Li Fong.
All right, wise guy.
Hey, Johnny, you gotta try
this pizza from New York.
- It's the best I've ever had.
- Why would you ship pizza from New York?
Everybody knows
the best pizza's in Encino.
No, there's no comparison. I'm telling ya.
- Wait, dude, that's it.
- What?
- Our new business idea.
- What are you talking about?
We open our own pizza place.
We call it Miyagi-Dough.
Uh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, get it? Like Miyagi-Do,
but dough, like pizza dough.
Y-Yeah, yeah, I get it.
It's disrespectful.
- To pizza?
- To Mr. Miyagi.
Mr. Miyagi didn't like pizza?
Yeah, Johnny, you know what?
I'm gonna heat the pizza.
Miyagi-Dough.
Pepperoni's your best defense.
Slice first, slice hard, no anchovies.
This is a billion-dollar idea, LaRusso.
- Miyagi-Dough. Miyagi-Dough.
- [song ends]
Olives on, olives off. [mutters]
♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ I had a vision ♪
♪ I had to work for this and you didn't ♪
♪ I had to bleed
Still got the stitches ♪
♪ I learned to swim
From all your burned bridges ♪
♪ Say you're the poet and the prophet ♪
♪ But you never saw me coming ♪
♪ Always starving for attention
Nothing you can do ♪
- ♪ Oh-oh ♪
- ♪ I feel it in my bones ♪
♪ Won't bring me down
No, not even close ♪
♪ Go ahead and throw your stones ♪
♪ But you can't stop this
You can't stop this ♪
♪ You can't stop this ♪
♪ Oh-oh
You won't break me ♪
♪ I won't back down ♪
♪ I just can't shake this feeling like ♪
♪ I'm going so high, I got no doubt ♪
♪ This life ain't got no ceiling like ♪
♪ It won't break me
I won't back down ♪
♪ I just can't shake this feeling like ♪
♪ I'm going so high, I got no doubt ♪
♪ This life ain't got no ceiling like ♪
♪ You can't stop this ♪